

DAMIAN M. BUZINK

Gameplay programmer

@ dbuzink@gmail.com

J +31636536889

O dmbuzink dmbuzink.github.io Eindhoven, The Netherlands

TECH STACK

Unreal Engine

Unity

C++

Python Java

Javascript\Typescript

.NET Node.js

Angular Docker

SQL Server Blazor

MySql MongoDb

Neo4j

SKILLS

Software design

Full stack development

Algorithm expertise

Leadership

LANGUAGES

Dutch: Native English: Fluent

FAVORITES GAMES

- Persona 3
- Assassin's Creed 2
- Zero Escape: Virtue's Last Reward
- God of War (2018)
- Baldur's Gate 3
- Astral Chain
- 13 Sentinels Disco Elvsium
- Fire Emblem: Three
- Houses
- Ghost of Tsushima

ABOUT ME

I am Damian Mitchel Buzink and I am 24 years old. Ever since I was a little kid I have loved games and wanted to become a game developer, even though I did not even know what such a job entailed. Later as I got interested in technology and learned more about game development, I wanted to become a gameplay programmer. I hope to one day become a lead gameplay programmer.

EXPERIENCE

Software developer internship | Asamco B.V.

1 02 2021 - 08 2021

Breda, The Netherlands

 Developed a new version of their Loan Management System. Consisting of a new SDK with core functionality, a website and a web API with the SDK functionality.

Software developer internship | CM.com

1 08 2019 - 01 2020

Breda, The Netherlands

• Developed a product generic invoice system.

EDUCATION

Master Computer Science and Engineering | Eindhoven University of Technology

1 09 2021 - 08 2023

Eindhoven, The Netherlands

- Thesis: The effect of area preservation on polygon simplification
- Focus: Algorithms

Bachelor Software Development | Avans University of Applied Sciences

1 08 2017 - 08 2021

Breda. The Netherlands

 Minor: HBO-TOP Minor Computer science and Engineering (special pre-master program for high performing HBO students)

PROJECTS

Aigez Brain Trainer | 🌐





- A serious game intended for lonely elderly people created for a school assignment. The main gameplay consists of six different minigames, with a leaderboard as a multiplayer component, and included a small story tying the gameplay together. Created as part of a team, which I lead. Only available in Dutch.
- Created in Unity with a small server app developed with .NET.

The Heiress on Ice





- A small game demo, where you play as a figure skater fighting enemies. In the game you do more damage, the higher your velocity. You can keep your velocity high by finding a path through the enemies, as turning slows you down a lot, which is enabled by the ejection that happens after you attack.
- Solo-developed in Unreal Engine 5.